admeta.com 2019-12-24

# Privacy Policy | WideOrbit

### **Personal Information**

You may choose to provide personal information (such as your name, address, telephone number and email address) on this Web site. Here are some of the ways you may provide the information and the types of information you may submit. We also tell you how we may use the information.

###  **Contact Us**

If you email us through the “Contact Us” link on this site, we ask you for information such as your name and email address so we can respond to your questions and comments. You may choose to provide additional information as well.

###  **Demo Request**

If you email us through the “Demonstration Request” link on this site, we ask you for information such as your name, company, address, phone number and email address so we can respond to your questions and comments. You may choose to provide additional information as well.

###  **Questionnaires and Surveys**

We occasionally may ask visitors to our Web site to complete online surveys and opinion polls about their activities, attitudes and interests. These surveys help us serve you better and improve the usefulness of our site. In conducting these surveys we may ask you for your name and email address. We do not keep any personal information about you in connection with your participation in a WideOrbit.com survey unless you specifically agree to provide that information.

###  **Non-Personal Information**

We collect certain aggregate and non-personal information when you visit this Web site. Aggregate and non-personal information does not relate to a single identifiable visitor. It tells us such things as how many users visited our site and the pages accessed. By collecting this information, we learn how to best tailor our Web site to our visitors. We collect this information either through “cookie” technology or with “web beacons,” as explained below.

###  **Interest based advertising on internet**

We collect anonymous data for each user that is used to show the best possible advertisement at each page view on the internet. At the same time we respect our users’ privacy and understand that some users don’t want any data to be collected about them. To opt out go to [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). WO Programmatic Digital adheres to the European Principals of the EDAA Online Behavioral Advertising (OBA) Framework.

###  **Cookies**

This Cookie Policy explains how WideOrbit Sweden AB and its group companies (collectively “WideOrbit”, we”, “us”, and “our”) use cookies and similar technologies to recognise you when you visit our website, available at https://www.wideorbit.com/, and its sub-domains (“Website”), or when you interact with an advertsisement served through WO Programmatic Digital, our proprietary digital advertising management technology platform (the “Platform”). It explains what these technologies are and why we use them, as well as your rights to control our use of them.

Like many companies, we use browser cookies on this Web site. Browser cookies are bits of text that are placed on your computer’s hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. We use browser cookies to tell us, for example, whether you’ve visited us before or if you’re a new visitor and to help us identify site features in which you may have the greatest interest. Browser cookies may enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site.

What are cookies and why they are used?  
Cookies are small data files that are placed on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website or use an online service. Cookies are widely used by online service providers in order to make their websites or services work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide reporting information.

Cookies set by WideOrbit on its Website and Platforms are called “first party cookies”. We use first party cookies for several reasons. Some cookies are required for technical reasons in order for our Website, Platform and related services to operate Other cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience of our Website , or to create analytics about online campaigns run by customers who use our Platform.

Cookies set by parties other than the website or service owner are called “third party cookies”. Third party cookies often enable third party features or functionality to be provided on the website or service you are using (e.g. like advertising, interactive content and analytics). The third parties that set these cookies can use them to recognise your computer both when it visits the website or service in question and alsoand when it uses certain other websites or services.

The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new browser cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new browser cookie, and how to disable existing browser cookies. Remember though, without browser cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of all our Web site features.

###  **Web Beacons**

Certain pages on our site contain “web beacons” (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). These web beacons allow third parties to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third party. We use log files to store the data that is collected through web beacons.

###  **Information We Share**

We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information about our Web site visitors, except as described here. We may share information provided by our visitors to WideOrbit.com with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf. These service providers are contractually restricted from using or disclosing the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.

###  **Links to Other Sites**

We provide links to other Web sites for your convenience and information. These sites may have their own privacy statements in place, which we recommend you review if you visit any linked Web sites. We are not responsible for the content of linked sites or any use of the sites.

###  **Children’s Privacy**

This Web site is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen on the site. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a visitor under the age of thirteen on the site, we will delete the information from our records.

###  **WideOrbit California Resident Privacy Notice**

This California Resident Privacy Notice supplements the information and disclosures contained in our Privacy Policy. It applies to individuals residing in California from whom we collect Personal Information as a business under California law.

 **Personal Information Collection, Disclosure, and Sale**

For the purposes of this notice, **Personal Information** means information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household, or as otherwise defined by the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (California Civil Code §§ 1798.100 to 1798.199) and its implementing regulations, as amended or superseded from time to time (“ **CCPA** ”). 

Personal Information does not include information that is:

  * Lawfully made available from government records.
  * Deidentified or aggregate information.
  * Otherwise excluded from the scope of the CCPA.

In the preceding twelve months since this notice was last updated, we have collected Personal Information from you, your devices, our affiliates, third parties, and from categories of sources otherwise described in our Privacy Policy. The examples of Personal Information provided for each category reflect each category’s statutory definition and may not reflect all of the specific types of Personal Information associated with each category. We have collected, disclosed for a business purpose, or sold the following categories of Personal Information in the preceding twelve months since this notice was last updated:

 **Category**|  **We Collect**|  **We Disclose**|  **We Sell**  
---|---|---|---  
  
 **A. Identifiers**  
Examples: Name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, internet protocol address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers.| Yes| Yes| Yes  
  
 **B. Categories of Personal Information in Cal. Civ. Code Section 1798.80(e)**  
Examples: Name, signature, social security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver’s license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information.| Yes| Yes| No  
  
 **C. Characteristics of Protected Classifications under California or Federal Law**  
Examples: Age (over 40), and sex (including gender)| Yes| Yes| Yes  
  
 **D. Commercial Information**  
Examples: Records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.| Yes| Yes| Yes  
  
 **E. Biometric Information**  
Examples: Physiological, biological, or behavioral characteristics, including DNA, that can be used, singly or in combination with each other or with other identifying data, to establish individual identity, such as imagery of the iris, retina, fingerprint, face, hand, palm, vein patterns, and voice recordings, from which an identifier template, such as a faceprint, a minutiae template, or a voiceprint, can be extracted, and keystroke patterns or rhythms, gait patterns or rhythms, and sleep, health, or exercise data that contain identifying information.| No| N/A| N/A  
  
 **F. Internet or Other Electronic Network Activity Information**  
Examples: Browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an internet website, application or advertisement.| Yes| Yes| Yes  
  
 **G. Geolocation Data**  
Example: Precise physical location.| Yes| Yes| Yes  
  
 **H. Sensory Information**  
Examples: Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information.| No| N/A| N/A  
  
 **I. Professional or employment-related information.**  
Examples: Job application or resume information, past and current job history, and job performance information.| No| N/A| N/A  
  
 **J. Non-Public Education Information (as defined in 20 U.S.C. 1232g; 34 C.F.R. Part 99).**  
Examples: Records that are directly related to a student maintained by an educational agency or institution or by a party acting for the agency or institution.| No| N/A| N/A  
  
 **K. Inferences Drawn from Personal Information**  
Examples: Consumer profiles reflecting a consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, preferences, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes.| Yes| Yes| Yes  
  
 **Use of Personal Information**

We collect, use, and disclose your Personal Information in accordance with the purposes disclosed in our Privacy Policy and for the specific business purposes below:

  1. Providing Services: Providing our services.
  2. Communicating: Communicating with you, providing you with updates and other information relating to our services, providing information that you request, responding to comments and questions, and otherwise providing customer support.
  3. Connecting Third Party Services: Facilitating the connection of third-party services or applications.
  4. Marketing: Marketing purposes, such as developing and providing promotional and advertising materials that may be useful, relevant, valuable or otherwise of interest to you.
  5. Personalization: Personalizing your experience on our services such as presenting tailored content.
  6. Facilitating Payments: Facilitating transactions and payments.
  7. Deidentification and Aggregation: De-identifying and aggregating information collected through our services and using it for any lawful purpose.
  8. Safety Issues: Responding to trust and safety issues that may arise.
  9. Compliance: For compliance purposes, including enforcing our Terms of Service or other legal rights, or as may be required by applicable laws and regulations or requested by any judicial process or governmental agency.
  10. Auditing Interactions: Auditing related to a current interaction with you and concurrent transactions, including, but not limited to, counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards.
  11. Fraud and Incident Prevention: Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity.
  12. Debugging: Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
  13. Transient Use: Short-term, transient use.
  14. Contracting Vendors: Contracting with service providers to perform services on our behalf or on their behalf, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the business or service provider.
  15. Research: Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration.
  16. Product Improvement: Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of our services, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance our services.
  17. Enabling Transactions: Otherwise enabling or effecting, directly or indirectly, a commercial transaction.
  18. Notified Purpose: For other purposes for which we provide specific notice at the time the information is collected.

 **Collection and Disclosure of Personal Information**

In the preceding twelve months since this notice was last updated, we have collected Personal Information from the following categories of sources:

A. You/Your Devices: You or your devices directly.  
B. Users: Other users of our services.  
C. Affiliates: Affiliates.  
D. Government: Government entities.  
E. Resellers: Consumer data resellers.  
F. Partners: Business partners.  
G. Public: Publicly accessible sources.

Pursuant to our Privacy Policy, we share your Personal Information with the following categories of third parties:

I. Advertisers: Advertising networks.  
II. ISPs: Internet service providers.  
III. Analytics Providers: Data analytics providers.  
IV. Social Networks: Social networks.  
V. Resellers: Consumer data resellers.  
VI. Affiliates: Affiliates.  
VII. Vendors: Vendors and service providers.  
VIII. Integrated Third Parties: Third parties integrated into our services.  
IX. Third Parties as Legally Required: Third parties as required by law and similar disclosures.  
X. Third Parties in Merger/Acquisition: Third parties in connection with a merger, sale, or asset transfer.  
XI. Third Parties with Consent: Other third parties for whom we have obtained your permission to disclose your Personal Information.

 **Your California Privacy Rights**

If you are a California resident, you may exercise the following rights.

 **Right to Know and Access**. You may submit a verifiable request for information regarding the: (1) categories of Personal Information collected, sold, or disclosed by us; (2) purposes for which categories of Personal Information are collected or sold by us; (3) categories of sources from which we collect Personal Information; and (4) specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you during the past twelve months.

 **Right to Delete**. Subject to certain exceptions, you may submit a verifiable request that we delete Personal Information about you that we have collected from you. 

**Verification**. Requests for access to or deletion of Personal Information are subject to our ability to reasonably verify your identity in light of the information requested and pursuant to relevant CCPA requirements, limitations, and regulations. In order for us to verify your identity, you must (a) provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collect personal information or an authorized representative; and (b) describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it. We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you.

 **Right to Opt Out**. In some circumstances, you may opt out of the sale of your Personal Information. Click here to opt out of the sale of your Personal Information: Do Not Sell My Info. 

**Right to Equal Service and Price**. You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment for the exercise of your CCPA privacy rights, subject to certain limitations. 

**Shine the Light.** You may request information once per calendar year about our disclosures of certain categories of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to us in writing using the Contact Information section below.

 **Submit Requests**. To exercise your rights under the CCPA, please click here or contact us via our Contact Information section, or visit our website. 

**Authorizing an Agent** : To authorize an agent to make a request to know or delete on your behalf, please provide a written authorization signed by you and the authorized agent along with sufficient information to verify your identify to us via the Contact Information section. To authorize an agent to make an opt-out request on your behalf, please send a written authorization signed by you and the authorized agent to us via the Contact Information section.

 **Minors**  
We do not sell the Personal Information of minors under 16 years of age without affirmative authorization.

 **Do Not Track**

There is no accepted standard on how to respond to Do Not Track signals, and we do not respond to such signals.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about our processing activities, or you would like to exercise your privacy rights please email us at [privacy@wideorbit.com](mailto:privacy@wideorbit.com), or write to us at:

WideOrbit Inc. Attn: Legal Department, 1160 Battery St., Suite 300, San Francisco, CA 94111.

 **Last Updated:** December 23, 2019
